Rachel Ciarlante

rach.ciarlante@gmail.com

github.com/RachCiar ◆ codepen.io/artosCiarlante/ linkedin.com/in/rachelciarlante/ ◆ RachelCiarlante.com

Professional Summary

Recent Web Development graduate with over 20 years of experience in Business Administration. Qualified professional. Works well in teams and independently. Takes a pro-active approach to tasks. Very organized and detail oriented. A fast learner who loves challenges.

Education

Sullivan UniversityLouisville, KYAssociate of Science in Dynamic Web DevelopmentExpected June 2019Certificate in DraftingMarch 2012Diploma for Office SpecialistMarch 1988

Skills & Abilities

•	HTML/CSS3	•	Netbeans	•	Microsoft Office Suite
•	CSS Grid	•	Adobe Dream Weaver	•	Database Management
•	Bootstrap	•	Adobe Photoshop cc		& Reporting
•	JavaScript	•	Adobe After Effects cc	•	Logic and Algorithm
•	PHP	•	Adobe XD cc	•	UX/UI
•	MySQL	•	Adobe Animate cc	•	Office Management
•	WordPress	•	Java	•	Customer Focused
•	Visual Studio Code	•	SharePoint Services		

Experience

New Beginnings foundation Louisville, KY

Internship 3/2019 – Present

- Redesigned the NewBeginnings.foundation website using WordPress, Adobe XD, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Tested NBFS website for UX/UI design for launch.
- Improved WordPress skills by learning how to build a theme from scratch using Gulp, Node.js, and SASS.

Insight Communications

Louisville, KY

Executive Assistant for VP of Billing, Information Services, and Engineering

12/2006 - 05/2009

- Trained and provided Help Desk support for SharePoint Services 3.0.
- Created and designed SharePoint web sites.
- Provided administrative support to IT Department, other VPs, and managers as needed.
- Sorted, organized, and documented legal documents in SP for Senior VP.
- Researched, prepared reports, and assisted in projects for IT Department.
- Handled front-office and Back-office duties
- Trusted with personal and confidential information.

Rachel Ciarlante

rach.ciarlante@gmail.com
github.com/RachCiar ◆ codepen.io/artosCiarlante/
linkedin.com/in/rachelciarlante/◆ RachelCiarlante.com

Experience (cont.)

Jamestown of St. Matthews

Louisville, KY

Billing Manager

11/2005 - 12/2006

- Responsible for developing and implementing invoicing procedures for Gas usage of 650 units in two apartment complexes.
- Assisted Managers of both complexes with special projects.
- Compiled weekly and monthly reports.
- Designed Daily Expense Control Ledger on Excel, which was adopted by the other apartment complexes that the company owned.

The Ice Cream Factory and Restaurant

Louisville, KY

Co-Owner

10/2001 - 05/2006

- Assisted with billing, daily sales, forecasting and marketing.
- Supervised and provided general office and budget support, including accounts payable.
- Designed promotional materials